java-scripts.net 2007-12-27

# Javascripts by Java-Scripts.net: Free javascripts, tutorials, examples, and resources.

Ads  
We use cookies to limit the number of popup ads that you may see while visiting our site. Some of our advertising partners may also deliver a cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. 

NOTE ON COOKIES:  
A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use the Java-scripts.net site. 

When joining our mailing list: Your personal information is never passed or sold to a third party for marketing or solicitation purposes unless you SPECIFICALLY request to be added though the DESIGNATED signup forms. 

We may elect to use a third party to help us with the distribution of our emails to you. However, this will be with the understanding that this third party keeps any information secure and uses it solely for the purpose of distributing our newsletter containing our content. Any such third party would be bound by our privacy policy with regard to the use of our membership list. Each mailing that we send to you has full instructions of how to unsubscribe from the mailing list should you elect to do so. 

Some of our 'site partners' and 'ad partners' include: 

PostMasterDirect, an opt-in mailing list maintenance company - Your name and/or email are NEVER passed on to this company unless you SPECIFICALLY request to be added though the DESIGNATED PostMasterDirect signup page. 

Your name and/or email are NEVER passed on to these companies unless you SPECIFICALLY request to be added though the DESIGNATED signup pages. 

From time to time some of our advertising partners may prompt you to enter your email address or other personal information via an ad on this site. Please refer to their privacy policy for their specific use of this information. 

From time to time we may need to use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

© 2007 [Javascripts](http://www.java-scripts.net/)   
Proudly Hosted by [HostDeparment](http://www.hostdepartment.com/)  
Now Viewing **[](http://www.java-scripts.net/privacy.phtml)**
